sergeant love it don't laugh at my
funeral that ain't her fellow bros we
are gathered here today to mourn for the
loss of a bro me a my own eulogy is a
sad day but I wouldn't be honored if you
my bros would lay me to rest here in the
bro cave right here right now I've made
my own I've dug my own grave nice but
I've got I've got also something to say
even though I've lost my dragon head I
still want to be considered a bro so in
my inventory I've got a dragon head and
it's called secret bro and that means
I'm I've lost it not one of us he's not
what a night it means that I will not
demise any bro hand on heart that's good
to know
I will be a bro all right all right
there you go one for friendship so I
shot at you oh thank you okay yep thank
you the stake in the rocket steak steak
rockets and and the forged friendship
anyone want to say a few words about us
no sorry dude you're done get in the
hole
I don't mind I got I got a little
something also called Okaloosa alright
so Green was a great leader oh the one
that converted me I
I was normal and lost and then one day I
was found with a dragon head so part of
this team and in his death and loss I
vowed to be the new leader no cookie
that you wouldn't do that okay well I
was thinking we just fight him but okay
okay I won't do that oh okay well then
rest may he rest in peace all right if I
can make my how do you even get up here
up to there let's find your dad okay I'm
officially dead check it out
welcome back to another episode of
hermit craft I totally blend in with
everything gray now I really thought I
might make it to the end but I didn't I
got I got done dead by by a pretty over
killed trap and well explosive to say
the least
I lost everything and I and I mean
everything it took me a full day in real
life to get everything back where it was
before so I've got myself and I've even
renamed everything so I've got a sword
scribe going on here try and subscribe
I've got fax machine to subscribe Axia
wasn't very inventive with some of these
names silk machine too and the gravel
and sand machine too as well then once I
got everything back I headed in over
here and you can see there's loads of
schalke boxes this is exactly what we're
going to be doing today I have been
trading for almost 24 hours and I have
got schalke box after shocker box of
stuff now this is the stuff that's going
in Sahara this is the big restock the
I was telling you guys about in the last
episode that I didn't manage to do but
you can see I have been trading and
trading and trading and trading and
trading and trading and dreaming and I
didn't even make a dent in it look look
at all this I've got so many emerald
blocks here and here and still loads us
I just I basically ran out of chakra
boxes but at the same time miss kau has
also been trying to restock Sahara and
we're not really very good at
communicating at the moment so what I'm
going to do is show you something
amazing I have upgraded my chair yet
again this is looking like the game of
Thrones
throne I love where this is going with
the chair I don't even know how I can
make this any bigger at this point
okay so I've upgraded the chair but what
we're gonna do in here is a big Sahara
tracker before we get into really trying
to demise everyone else of course I am a
secret bro
so I'm not gonna be going after my my
bro friends maybe maybe until they're
the last if they like the last ones
alive then I really don't have much of a
choice but until that time secret bro
I'm not going for my bros so we're gonna
make a huge table of stock this is going
to keep track of everything and also
show what we've got already you got to
understand that restocking suhara
isn't just as easy as you think you
don't just walk up and throw a bunch of
items into the system although I wish it
was like that but hopefully this will
give us enough stuck Wow look at that
okay let's kick this off okay so you put
the item here which Arctic is collecting
it and then you put the stock so let's
for example golden carrots has been
collected by green and the stock is
right here and then we just make our way
down and continue so I've actually
collected quite a lot of things other
than golden carrots I've got loads of
bricks and I've got loads of quartz
blocks as well although it takes a lot
longer to get quartz than it does bricks
there's loads of bricks and then I can
start putting in all the other things
that we need to collect so obviously
I've put some redstone here but there
are other things as well okay so
basically I didn't even scratch the
surface with how much stuff we collect I
there's still like four or five maybe
even more things that aren't on the list
but let's just start there because we've
made some pretty good progress and in
fact I can actually add this one here
which was collected by mumbo cuz this
has got observers in so I can pop that
there I'm actually gonna go and have to
get some scowler mumbo heads cuz I don't
really care around my own head which is
weird enough as it is so you can see
where we're going with this and
hopefully the other guys the other
architects I can let them know what this
is all about and maybe I'll even create
one on this side as well next to the
giant chair of oh my I love this chair
what's going on here okay so that's kind
of the Sahara admin out of the way we
obviously did quite a lot of architects
stuff here oh my goodness Skaar that
that actually brings me to a really good
point I'm meeting up with good times
with Skaar right now because obviously
both of us are on the dead team and I
haven't actually seen Skaar in a long
long time
so we're gonna meet up and we're going
to of course in our first episode where
we're dead we're gonna plan someone's
demise but it can't be a bro
so that gives us two options let's go
and find Skaar wherever he is and let's
get demising yeah I'm surprised why is
this the crypt of the ripped as in
that's he up to the room the art oh you
know what I knew you had this skin on
but I've only just understood the pun of
our IP ripped
Shh stray over my head dude I now i'm
r.i.p i want to get ripped well you can
just head on down here we've got the
ribs pool
we got the rib benchpress pumps and well
this should be a good place to discuss
what we planned so i message to you
because obviously I'm dead you're dead
I haven't checked you for a while so you
want to go and do my some people oh I've
been dreaming of killing people
dude it's it's been a dream for weeks
that's why ass whirring have you demised
anyone yet at all no no you would like
one of the first to go so that's a
little disappointing I mean I mean I've
been doing some building I've been doing
some cool building does that make up for
anything okay well yeah you want to show
me what you've been doing I took is that
your building over there that's the one
I saw floating and now there's a giant
lightning strike on it so let's go over
to the graveyard and check who is
actually alive because I'm not actually
that up to date so if that's a sign it
means that they're alive if there's a
head it means they're dead so someone
has buried me here but I've actually
already got a grave so this this is like
a fake body it's got to be so who's
alive we got mumbo is scowl okay so we
got a bit you I'm a secret bro okay oh
oh it's back yeah I won't I won't go and
for any of my bros so it's got to be
someone that's not a dragon bro
Congress meetups can't go for mumbo
cargo Fisker so that leaves Joe doc and
corrales docs online and I have no idea
where Joe's bases so I don't even know
how to get him he's a nomad
he's just roaming well that's actually a
really good way to not get demise
because I can't target him so that
leaves Corrales bases I don't think we
can go after doc while he's online
that's we need to have some time to trap
because I think what we've just done is
we've just put together a team of you
and I have two of the worst red stoners
on the entire we're gonna need at least
like three hours to put some
together but I have got an idea I have
made a trap before we're gonna need to
go and get a lot of puffer fish because
I think that's gonna be one of the best
ways to get him all right also on a plus
side I do have nearly unlimited redstone
supplies so that's a plus
all right let's get across his base I
haven't been here in a really long time
but as I was flying in I was just like
whoa this is really grown since I was
last here and corrales is like barniz
just stayed the same and then there's a
dire I console I never thought you'd be
able to make anything so good out of
diorite I have such conflicting feelings
so beautiful but also made out of like
diver rice but honestly if anyone can
pull it off it's the beat man mr. B and
he did a great job on that
you know actually before we go to cross
his house my favorite thing that b-dubs
has done was actually in the first house
I think is this one is it this one I
think this is his first house my
favorite thing is his toilet here it's
like the button the button as I did this
on stream here plush here whoa hold on
let me give you a courtesy flush Scott
you guys see this but there's like there
you go
but there's straight-up look poop I knew
it no there's a there's a there's a well
there is there is poop down here but
there's actually like a sewer this
beat-up she's being like making a sewer
for his base yeah you haven't seen this
yet no this is amazing no I frequent for
this area oh I love this it's so cold
and damp it just fits our demeanor and
our personalities now do you want to see
something magical what I didn't I didn't
push this but I've been told about it
are you ready for it
what which I don't know what it's gonna
do but something's gonna happen when I
do this okay
well maybe not that time let me do it
again this
Yara's on streams is this missus b-dubs
cuz I'm not going after a bro no this is
not the B dubs this is Kraus you can
tell by the beautiful modern aesthetic
we flushed ourselves down the toilet
into a sewer how did you find out about
this dude viewers are the biggest tattle
tales in the world when it comes to
streams I know right I'm like hey guys
don't tell anyone about this what do
they do straight in the comments
hey guess what's going in your base I
made a trap oh yes they very much
informed me this on stream and this is
really cool their information paid off
cuz this is awesome this is exactly what
we need to trap as long as he actually
comes down here alright we need to
figure out how we're gonna pufferfish
trap this the door is here the
likelihood is that he will maybe walk
across here so we could use this as the
trapping mechanism
what does Corrales love more than
anything in the world meatballs
run you know the run the game is called
the other Swedish meatball does he still
play it I I think so right I mean I
closed for a while ah I was thinking we
could lure him with like free tokens but
they up but it's really just a trap of
death Oh where's this go oh my goodness
This Is It this is it
I like like I did in the gteen base when
you go up it'll activate it'll seal off
the top and release all the puffer fish
genius um well what if you what if he
comes up he's bubbling his Kraus he's
rolling his cruisin and he comes up like
in we build like a little house around
like a tank and he just gets launched
into a tank of puffers hanging out but
he also might see it like a new
structure that's also a thing we could
disguise it as one of these houses we
could we could just build we could fill
it with so many puffer fish and he won't
even he won't even have a choice you
might be able to swim out or anything
you know what that's by far the easiest
way we're gonna make like true barium
full of puffer fish
we're gonna disguise it as one of these
original houses and they won't even know
oh yeah I think yeah yeah I think
that'll be good plus we don't have to do
that much redstone yeah yeah we don't
even have to get too creative well this
is this is perfect
several hours of swimming for puffer
fish what have we got how many have we
got
I have 71 did we really get that many
oh wait that's it's tangos what the
there we go oh wow we really did get
along yeah so what we're gonna do is
we're gonna imitate that exact house
over there but obviously like we can't
we can't like have any windows in it so
it will look maybe a little bit
suspicious but hopefully it would go
down quite well can't believe this I
can't believe they just have an exit
like this so this should be really
simple this is a simple build there we
go one two three this is the most
complicated you've just saved us hours
of redstone pain you know I'm just glad
to be of service
we don't need redstone to demise people
look at been going to town on this stuff
[Laughter]
I nailed it that work is trap that's
ever been made honestly the easiest but
most efficient and callous will do you
need to do this properly we need a
couple of torches the only thing we
can't put in here are the windows but if
it's done right like we won't have to do
any of this stuff right so what we do
now is we are going to put the
pufferfish inside all of these
billion we're gonna go overkill like all
the pufferfish we need to flood this
right or our poor puffer Zola
yeah we can do that oh my goodness we're
gonna have to test it out yeah I don't
want to we're gonna have to draw for
this pleasure of demising into this
buffer tank we still got like 40 more of
these yeah we're gonna keep going
it's calm we should we should rename one
of them just one puffer fish each and if
we get the kill like we have to give
each other no there's never enough okay
okay I think that's enough I think we
could test it I can't I can't finish
this I can't get up there
this box just got a lot more suspicious
seeing as it every time you go near it
it goes I mean maybe it's the haunted
house
I think we've just got to be fortunate
wait hold on come over here
Crassus houses over there yeah from his
house
it doesn't look actually it doesn't look
out of place at all every Oh No
honestly doesn't we obviously know that
it is out of place because it's got no
windows but if you're just I don't think
he's gonna notice at all and unless he
has a reason to come over here and I
can't see why it doesn't make a noise
here Oh
Bish's puffer fish that you know what
I'm gonna I'm gonna throw this out there
that might be a dead giveaway get really
close did you eat it sorry actually get
really close it doesn't make a noise
right I'm taking my stuff
and I'm gonna set my school and we're
gonna test this thing out you know that
was the longest Minecraft day what's
like let the cat out do you want me to
flush you or you want to flush me or we
flush together let's flush together I'm
gonna come in wait wait wait wait wait
wait Scott what have you got in your
inventory and where are we going okay
good good good
what wipe your feet you barbarian okay
so basically he's building away any guys
I'm joining you I'm joining it's so bad
oh I love her fish I love cheese I'm her
hood really surprised if he makes it out
of there alive no I think we should
leave now before Corrales comes online
probably a good idea right we got to
make sure that this gets left in a
really clean state and then vanos oh
it's so much forgetting something we're
forgetting something
we need a we need an anvil so that's
still on true the rename a puffer fish
each if one of our puffer fish kills
Corrales you owe me a hundred diamonds
or I owe you hundred diamonds okay all
right I'm good with that
I'm gonna name mine a poor choice of
exit fortress of exit yeah Corrales was
killed by a poor choice of exit all
right got mine I gotta go with mrs. puff
was way easier than I thought that was
actually yeah no redstone required it
took a long time to like set up to get
all the puffer fish and stuff but once
that was done easy-peasy
and now we have proof do the cleanup and
that's basically it we're cleaned up see
people have had such a hard time getting
people demised but look at this I
we're digging it up scar but if he
doesn't fall for it's gonna be really
embarrassed
that is true that is true but I look at
that I see a work of beauty
it looks like looks like an outhouse in
a way when you look at in a certain way
honestly looks like it fits in perfectly
with these other houses and you would
look I don't think you'd look at it
twice and you'd have to go right up to
it to hear the puffer fish so I'm
feeling pretty hopeful mission
accomplished dude right so we don't
we're not gonna we're not gonna like
high-five because we're just bomb we're
rip we're gonna chest box ready for this
yes I'm ready I'm ready
that's right that's right that's how we
will save dad so we just pause straight
through each other
that's that is it that is a detail of
truth right there okay all right thank
you scar let's get out of here before
someone logs online okay now that we've
done our first demise trap there's one
item of business left I need to head
over here to I can't believe it we've
gone a full circle year round it's now
time for the secret santa 2019 we had
secrets out to 2018 in the same series
so okay you have to put place your name
inside the dispenser I actually don't
have any levels I'm just gonna pop a
green head in here okay hopefully that's
enough cuz I died to the pufferfish
I've got nothing so hopefully that makes
sense and then I think that's it so when
it comes to it you draw the name you
just I think you just press the button
you get a name for your secret santa no
pressing these buttons yet and then you
press these and it tells you something
oh wait there's a totally a book here
that I haven't read all you need to do
is enter your name on a piece of paper
already failed that one place your name
into the dispensers provided wait until
after the given time to draw your Secret
Santa after this date you may draw your
Secret Santa by pressing a rat a button
at random from the name dispensers you
must then press the button on the
opposite side at random what gift you
give them in time for Christmas note if
you don't get anything from a dispenser
please try the one next to it okay enjoy
false you get the name then you do this
but I have to wait until the day I don't
know what date that is
but it's certainly not yet but that is
basically where we're going to end this
episode because we've actually done a
lot we started restocking Sahara we
upgraded our chair the most important
thing of the day and we have officially
set up to demise Corrales unless
something goes horribly wrong I think
that's really devious what me and Skaar
did was so basic it just might work but
we'll have to see also don't tell
Corrales you know what I'm just gonna
wait until I know this has either been
found or done before I even upload it
that way you can't spoil it thank you
very much for watching add good
[Music]